[Its National Wear Blue Day! Celebrate with a New Heather Blue Sweatshirt!](https://georgenotfound.shop/products/georgenotfound-black-logo-blue-sweatshirt)

* Shop
    
    Shop
    
    * Shop
        
        Shop

    * GNF Things
        
        GNF Things

* Partners
    
    Partners

Country/region
--------------

Afghanistan (USD $) Åland Islands (USD $) Albania (USD $) Algeria (USD $) Andorra (USD $) Angola (USD $) Anguilla (USD $) Antigua & Barbuda (USD $) Argentina (USD $) Armenia (USD $) Aruba (USD $) Ascension Island (USD $) Australia (USD $) Austria (USD $) Azerbaijan (USD $) Bahamas (USD $) Bahrain (USD $) Bangladesh (USD $) Barbados (USD $) Belarus (USD $) Belgium (USD $) Belize (USD $) Benin (USD $) Bermuda (USD $) Bhutan (USD $) Bolivia (USD $) Bosnia & Herzegovina (USD $) Botswana (USD $) Brazil (USD $) British Indian Ocean Territory (USD $) British Virgin Islands (USD $) Brunei (USD $) Bulgaria (USD $) Burkina Faso (USD $) Burundi (USD $) Cambodia (USD $) Cameroon (USD $) Canada (USD $) Cape Verde (USD $) Caribbean Netherlands (USD $) Cayman Islands (USD $) Central African Republic (USD $) Chad (USD $) Chile (USD $) China (USD $) Christmas Island (USD $) Cocos (Keeling) Islands (USD $) Colombia (USD $) Comoros (USD $) Congo - Brazzaville (USD $) Congo - Kinshasa (USD $) Cook Islands (USD $) Costa Rica (USD $) Côte d’Ivoire (USD $) Croatia (USD $) Curaçao (USD $) Cyprus (USD $) Czechia (USD $) Denmark (USD $) Djibouti (USD $) Dominica (USD $) Dominican Republic (USD $) Ecuador (USD $) Egypt (USD $) El Salvador (USD $) Equatorial Guinea (USD $) Eritrea (USD $) Estonia (USD $) Eswatini (USD $) Ethiopia (USD $) Falkland Islands (USD $) Faroe Islands (USD $) Fiji (USD $) Finland (USD $) France (USD $) French Guiana (USD $) French Polynesia (USD $) French Southern Territories (USD $) Gabon (USD $) Gambia (USD $) Georgia (USD $) Germany (USD $) Ghana (USD $) Gibraltar (USD $) Greece (USD $) Greenland (USD $) Grenada (USD $) Guadeloupe (USD $) Guatemala (USD $) Guernsey (USD $) Guinea (USD $) Guinea-Bissau (USD $) Guyana (USD $) Haiti (USD $) Honduras (USD $) Hong Kong SAR (USD $) Hungary (USD $) Iceland (USD $) India (USD $) Indonesia (USD $) Iraq (USD $) Ireland (USD $) Isle of Man (USD $) Israel (USD $) Italy (USD $) Jamaica (USD $) Japan (USD $) Jersey (USD $) Jordan (USD $) Kazakhstan (USD $) Kenya (USD $) Kiribati (USD $) Kosovo (USD $) Kuwait (USD $) Kyrgyzstan (USD $) Laos (USD $) Latvia (USD $) Lebanon (USD $) Lesotho (USD $) Liberia (USD $) Libya (USD $) Liechtenstein (USD $) Lithuania (USD $) Luxembourg (USD $) Macao SAR (USD $) Madagascar (USD $) Malawi (USD $) Malaysia (USD $) Maldives (USD $) Mali (USD $) Malta (USD $) Martinique (USD $) Mauritania (USD $) Mauritius (USD $) Mayotte (USD $) Mexico (USD $) Moldova (USD $) Monaco (USD $) Mongolia (USD $) Montenegro (USD $) Montserrat (USD $) Morocco (USD $) Mozambique (USD $) Myanmar (Burma) (USD $) Namibia (USD $) Nauru (USD $) Nepal (USD $) Netherlands (USD $) New Caledonia (USD $) New Zealand (USD $) Nicaragua (USD $) Niger (USD $) Nigeria (USD $) Niue (USD $) Norfolk Island (USD $) North Macedonia (USD $) Norway (USD $) Oman (USD $) Pakistan (USD $) Palestinian Territories (USD $) Panama (USD $) Papua New Guinea (USD $) Paraguay (USD $) Peru (USD $) Philippines (USD $) Pitcairn Islands (USD $) Poland (USD $) Portugal (USD $) Qatar (USD $) Réunion (USD $) Romania (USD $) Russia (USD $) Rwanda (USD $) Samoa (USD $) San Marino (USD $) São Tomé & Príncipe (USD $) Saudi Arabia (USD $) Senegal (USD $) Serbia (USD $) Seychelles (USD $) Sierra Leone (USD $) Singapore (USD $) Sint Maarten (USD $) Slovakia (USD $) Slovenia (USD $) Solomon Islands (USD $) Somalia (USD $) South Africa (USD $) South Georgia & South Sandwich Islands (USD $) South Korea (USD $) South Sudan (USD $) Spain (USD $) Sri Lanka (USD $) St. Barthélemy (USD $) St. Helena (USD $) St. Kitts & Nevis (USD $) St. Lucia (USD $) St. Martin (USD $) St. Pierre & Miquelon (USD $) St. Vincent & Grenadines (USD $) Sudan (USD $) Suriname (USD $) Svalbard & Jan Mayen (USD $) Sweden (USD $) Switzerland (USD $) Taiwan (USD $) Tajikistan (USD $) Tanzania (USD $) Thailand (USD $) Timor-Leste (USD $) Togo (USD $) Tokelau (USD $) Tonga (USD $) Trinidad & Tobago (USD $) Tristan da Cunha (USD $) Tunisia (USD $) Türkiye (USD $) Turkmenistan (USD $) Turks & Caicos Islands (USD $) Tuvalu (USD $) U.S. Outlying Islands (USD $) Uganda (USD $) Ukraine (USD $) United Arab Emirates (USD $) United Kingdom (USD $) United States (USD $) Uruguay (USD $) Uzbekistan (USD $) Vanuatu (USD $) Vatican City (USD $) Venezuela (USD $) Vietnam (USD $) Wallis & Futuna (USD $) Western Sahara (USD $) Yemen (USD $) Zambia (USD $) Zimbabwe (USD $)

Update country/region

Country/region
--------------

USD $ | United States

* Shop

* Partners

 Search[](https://georgenotfound.shop/cart)Cart

Item added to your cart
-----------------------

Check out

Continue shopping

Privacy policy
==============

This Privacy Policy describes how DreamBranding.com and georgenotfound.shop (the “Site” or “we”) collects, uses, and discloses your Personal Information when you visit or make a purchase from the Site.

Collecting Personal Information
===============================

When you visit the Site, we collect certain information about your device, your interaction with the Site, and information necessary to process your purchases. We may also collect additional information if you contact us for customer support. In this Privacy Policy, we refer to any information that can uniquely identify an individual (including the information below) as “Personal Information”. See the list below for more information about what Personal Information we collect and why.

Device information

* **Examples of Personal Information collected:** version of web browser, IP address, time zone, cookie information, what sites or products you view, search terms, and how you interact with the Site.
* **Purpose of collection:** to load the Site accurately for you, and to perform analytics on Sites usage to optimize our Site.
* **Source of collection:** Collected automatically when you access our Site using cookies, log files, web beacons, tags, or pixels.
* **Disclosure for a business purpose:** shared with our processor Shopify

Order information

* **Examples of Personal Information collected:** name, billing address, shipping address, payment information (including credit card numbers), email address, and phone number.
* **Purpose of collection:** to provide products or services to you to fulfill our contract, to process your payment information, arrange for shipping, and provide you with invoices and/or order confirmations, communicate with you, screen our orders for potential risk or fraud, and when in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.
* **Source of collection:** collected from you.
* **Disclosure for a business purpose:** shared with our processors Shopify, ShipStation and OrderHive.

Customer support information

* **Examples of Personal Information collected:** name, address, email and order number
* **Purpose of collection:** to provide customer support.
* **Source of collection:** collected from you.
* **Disclosure for a business purpose:** our internal Re:amaze team and our service provider Re:amaze as necessary

Minors
------

The Site is not intended for individuals under the age of legal consent. We do not intentionally collect Personal Information from children. If you are the parent or guardian and believe your child has provided us with Personal Information, please contact us at the address below to request deletion.

Sharing Personal Information
============================

We share your Personal Information with service providers to help us provide our services and fulfill our contracts with you, as described above. For example:

* We use Shopify to power our online store. You can read more about how Shopify uses your Personal Information here: [https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy](https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy).
* We may share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.
* The privacy policies of our other service providers can be seen here:  

Using Personal Information
--------------------------

We use your personal Information to provide our services to you, which includes: offering products for sale, processing payments, shipping and fulfillment of your order, and keeping you up to date on new products, services, and offers.

Lawful basis
------------

Pursuant to the General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”), if you are a resident of the European Economic Area (“EEA”), we process your personal information under the following lawful bases:

* Your consent;
* The performance of the contract between you and the Site;
* Compliance with our legal obligations;
* To protect your vital interests;
* To perform a task carried out in the public interest;
* For our legitimate interests, which do not override your fundamental rights and freedoms.

Retention
---------

When you place an order through the Site, we will retain your Personal Information for our records unless and until you ask us to erase this information. For more information on your right of erasure, please see the ‘Your rights’ section below.

Automatic decision-making
-------------------------

If you are a resident of the EEA, you have the right to object to processing based solely on automated decision-making (which includes profiling), when that decision-making has a legal effect on you or otherwise significantly affects you.

We do not engage in fully automated decision-making that has a legal or otherwise significant effect using customer data.

Our processor Shopify uses limited automated decision-making to prevent fraud that does not have a legal or otherwise significant effect on you.

Services that include elements of automated decision-making include:

* Temporary denylist of IP addresses associated with repeated failed transactions. This denylist persists for a small number of hours.
* Temporary denylist of credit cards associated with denylisted IP addresses. This denylist persists for a small number of days.

No Selling of Personal Information
==================================

Our Site does not sell Personal Information including Personal Information as defined by the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (“CCPA”).

Your rights
===========

GDPR
----

If you are a resident of the EEA, you have the right to access the Personal Information we hold about you, to port it to a new service, and to ask that your Personal Information be corrected, updated, or erased. If you would like to exercise these rights, please contact us through the Site contact page_._

Your Personal Information will be initially processed in Ireland and then will be transferred outside of Europe for storage and further processing, including to Canada and the United States. For more information on how data transfers comply with the GDPR, see Shopify’s GDPR Whitepaper: [https://help.shopify.com/en/manual/your-account/privacy/GDPR](https://help.shopify.com/en/manual/your-account/privacy/GDPR).

CCPA
----

If you are a resident of California, you may have the right to access the Personal Information we hold about you (also known as the ‘Right to Know’), to port it to a new service, and to ask that your Personal Information be corrected, updated, or erased. If you would like to exercise these rights, please contact us through the Site contact page.

Cookies
=======

A cookie is a small amount of information that’s downloaded to your computer or device when you visit our Site. We use a number of different cookies, including functional, performance, advertising, and social media or content cookies. Cookies make your browsing experience better by allowing the website to remember your actions and preferences (such as login and region selection). This means you don’t have to re-enter this information each time you return to the site or browse from one page to another. Cookies also provide information on how people use the website, for instance whether it’s their first time visiting or if they are a frequent visitor.

We use the following cookies to optimize your experience on our Site and to provide our services.

Cookies Necessary for the Functioning of the Store
--------------------------------------------------

| **Name** | **Function** |
| --- | --- |
| _\_ab_ | Used in connection with access to admin. |
| _\_secure\_session\_id_ | Used in connection with navigation through a storefront. |
| _cart_ | Used in connection with shopping cart. |
| _cart\_sig_ | Used in connection with checkout. |
| _cart\_ts_ | Used in connection with checkout. |
| _checkout\_token_ | Used in connection with checkout. |
| _secret_ | Used in connection with checkout. |
| _secure\_customer\_sig_ | Used in connection with customer login. |
| _storefront\_digest_ | Used in connection with customer login. |
| _\_shopify\_u_ | Used to facilitate updating customer account information. |

Reporting and Analytics
-----------------------

| **Name** | **Function** |
| --- | --- |
| _\_tracking\_consent_ | Tracking preferences. |
| _\_landing\_page_ | Track landing pages |
| _\_orig\_referrer_ | Track landing pages |
| _\_s_ | Shopify analytics. |
| _\_shopify\_fs_ | Shopify analytics. |
| _\_shopify\_s_ | Shopify analytics. |
| _\_shopify\_sa\_p_ | Shopify analytics relating to marketing & referrals. |
| _\_shopify\_sa\_t_ | Shopify analytics relating to marketing & referrals. |
| _\_shopify\_y_ | Shopify analytics. |
| _\_y_ | Shopify analytics. |

The length of time that a cookie remains on your computer or mobile device depends on whether it is a “persistent” or “session” cookie. Session cookies last until you stop browsing and persistent cookies last until they expire or are deleted. Most of the cookies we use are persistent and will expire between 30 minutes and two years from the date they are downloaded to your device.

You can control and manage cookies in various ways. Please keep in mind that removing or blocking cookies can negatively impact your user experience and parts of our website may no longer be fully accessible.

Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can choose whether or not to accept cookies through your browser controls, often found in your browser’s “Tools” or “Preferences” menu. For more information on how to modify your browser settings or how to block, manage or filter cookies can be found in your browser’s help file or through such sites as [www.allaboutcookies.org](https://shopdreambrand.myshopify.com/admin/settings/www.allaboutcookies.org).

Do Not Track
------------

Please note that because there is no consistent industry understanding of how to respond to “Do Not Track” signals, we do not alter our data collection and usage practices when we detect such a signal from your browser.

Changes
=======

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal, or regulatory reasons.

Contact
=======

For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by using the Contact page on the Site or by mail using the details provided below:

DreamBranding.com Privacy, 2200 Winter Springs Blvd, #106-234, Oviedo FL 32765, United States

Last updated: 2020-11-15

If you are not satisfied with our response to your complaint, you have the right to lodge your complaint with the relevant data protection authority. You can contact your local data protection authority.

George News
-----------

Contact
-------

Don't miss a drop - Subscribe to emails!
----------------------------------------

 Email

© 2024, [GeorgeNotFound](https://georgenotfound.shop/)

* Choosing a selection results in a full page refresh.
* Opens in a new window.
